coinclaim.io 2019-03-31

# Privacy | Coinclaim

## Privacy

CoinClaim.io (“CoinClaim.io” or “we”) manages and gives access to the CoinClaim.io website, currently located at the web address www.CoinClaim.io (the “Website”).

At CoinClaim.io, we are fully committed to respecting your privacy and to protecting any information that our clients provide. Your privacy and security are both our highest priorities and we make every effort to ensure that all the information provided by you is protected. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) is designed to inform you about the terms of treating your personal data.

**Personal Information**

In order to access the functionality of the Website, you will need to register. When registering, you will be asked to provide an email address and create a password. You may also choose to link to the Website using one of your accounts on the social networks, such as Twitter, Facebook and Google+.

**Record Collection**

We collect information from you when you make an account at CoinClaim, as well as in subsequent transactions. This includes your email and personal information, cryptocurrency wallet addresses and may include your browser’s name and technical information about your means of connection to our Website, in particular the operating system and the Internet service providers used, among other similar information.

**The Use of Collected Information**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register or use certain other site features. This might be for security reasons, to ask your opinion about the website, or it may be to keep you updated on any changes to the services provided on the Website. It may also be used to help provide you with the most personal experience possible while a CoinClaim customer. We may also send periodic emails with news and platform updates, or use this information to follow up with you following live chat or email.

**Security**

CoinClaim.io aims to protect the security of your information as much as we aim to protect our own information and network. We will not permit any third parties to contact you directly on an unsolicited basis in relation to their own products or services.

User data obtained by CoinClaim will never be transferred to a data broker or sold to a third[a] party for any reason.

CoinClaim’s privacy policy does not modify, supersede, or will ever be inconsistent with the policies of third party social media partners (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Telegram, etc.).

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. You should never disclose your account password to unauthorized parties. We use certain security measures to help keep your personal information safe, but we cannot guarantee that these measures will stop any users try to get around the privacy or security settings on the Website through unforeseen and/or illegal activity.

**Changes to the Policy**

This Policy may be amended at our full discretion without prior notice. We encourage you to review it periodically in order to be aware of the changes we may have made. Reading it carefully and checking for any modifications is your responsibility. By using the Website, you accept and agree to the Policy and the terms of use.
